Nice to meet you. I'm Harutora Kurobe.
Sui Kishida, second-year student.
Nice to meet you.
Sui's making a move on the newbie.
You didn't know? This guy's gay.
Does this mean you're into guys?
[Sorry.]
Welcome back.
When I'm with you, I smile for real.
Then can you take your mask off
when it's just us?
Huh?
Is that weird?
It's not weird, but...
Is that a no?
I wouldn't say no, but...
Please, Sui.
B-But it's embarrassing.
Sorry.
The way you get embarrassed, Sui...
I think I'm into it.
Huh?
I'm sorry.
I got carried away.
I'm gonna wash up.
What was that?
I couldn't sleep at all.
M-Morning.
Good morning, Sui. Bye then.
A dream? No, that definitely happened.
Sui.
I cleaned our room.
He must've just gotten
caught up in the moment.
Harutora's his usual self.
The way you get embarrassed, Sui...
I think I'm into it.
Sui, did you take a bath?
S-Sorry.
No, I'm actually... lucky.
My bad.
I meant I'm glad you didn't get hurt.
What a shock.
I thought you felt the same as me.
Huh?
No, nothing. Nothing at all.
Oh, right. Sui.
Why don't you go to the big bath?
Huh? That'd be awkward.
Everyone knows I'm gay.
Oh, so that's why...
Then in that case...
How about a tub in the room?
Huh?
An open-air bath.
H-Huh?
Or maybe...
a Goemon bath.
I think that side of you
is really charming, Harutora.
Huh?
You're serious, kind...
and a tiny bit quirky.
Yeah!
Harutora. Let's take a break.
Okay.
Wait, Sui. Isn't it tough for you
to keep coming to my solo practices?
Not at all. I enjoy it.
Besides, if I'm not here,
you'll push yourself too hard.
Oops, maybe I'm overstepping.
No, I'm happy you care.
Excuse me.
- Yes?
- Can you call that person over for us?
Sure. I'll go get him.
Those girls said they want to talk to you.
Why?
They want to get to know you.
No, not that.
Huh?
Harutora?
It hurts when you say things like that.
It really hurts.
Could we exchange numbers?
Sorry, I can't.
Huh?
What did he mean just now?
No way. My heart is...
Sui.
Dai-chan.
Something wrong with your chest?
Just heart palpitations...
You're like an old man.
Hey, so I saw you
hugging that newbie earlier.
You okay?
Remember when someone led you on
to make fun of you?
What? You actually fell for it?
Did you want a kiss?
Of course not.
There's no way anyone would like me.
Harutora's not that kind of guy.
H-He wouldn't do that.
O-Oh, right. That's true. Sorry.
I'm sure you're right,
but I think you should be careful
to avoid any misunderstandings.
Yeah, I know. I get it.
He just caught me because I stumbled.
I see.
That's good, then.
Sui, welcome back.
Sorry, did I wake you?
No, I was awake.
You're back late, huh?
Yeah, I was out studying.
If you're free this Sunday,
wanna go here?
[Relax your body and mind.]
It's a foot bath,
[A prime seat overlooking the sacred peak.]
and the view is amazing.
I thought you could relax there
without worrying about other people.
Harutora, you looked this up for me?
But you're so busy.
I think you should be careful
to avoid any misunderstandings.
Sorry. I think I'll pass.
Did I say something weird again?
No, it's because I have a test next week.
- So that's why you were studying.
- Yeah.
Got it.
Good night.
It's so pretty...
- Let's eat.
He's still not back yet.
[Sui Kishida - Harutora Kurobe]
Wow.
What are you doing, Sui?
Dai-chan.
You're on the committee too?
It's rough staying so late, huh?
It's not that...
Huh?
Seriously?
Hey.
Let's go over there. No one's around.
Come on.
I'll help you out.
You don't look like you mind.
Okay?
A smile doesn't always mean someone likes it.
Don't be rude to Sui.
W-Whoa. I was just kidding! It was a joke.
Sui, are you okay?
Y-Yeah. Thanks for defending me.
I'm totally fine.
He was just messing around.
But maybe he woke something inside of me.
Being pushed around wasn't bad.
Okay, then.
Harutora?
Huh?
N-No... stop.
I won't.
Sui, this is what you want, right?
No... No.
Stop. Stop it, Harutora.
Then tell him that too.
Say no when you mean no.
S-Sui...
I'm sorry.
I like you.
I... I like you.
I like you, Harutora.
So don't do things like this.
S-So stop being impulsive
and acting just on a whim.
I've had enough of feeling miserable.
- Here!
- I'm open!
Sorry!
Sui, I'm tired. Switch with me.
Y-Yeah, sure.
Let's go.
You can do it!
W-Wait! Oh, this isn't good.
Nice one!
Hurry! Faster!
Harutora.
Then tell him that too.
Say no when you mean no.
Sui.
Over here.
Okay.
Nice!
Dang it, are you serious?
What...
am I doing?
Wait, Harutora?
Sui.
I'm sorry.
Huh?
I've...
I've never really understood my own feelings.
But I finally realized it.
I...
I like you, Sui.
I like you. That's why I did that.
I'm sorry...
for hurting you.
Really?
Huh?
Are you really going to be my boyfriend?
Really?
Of course I will.
Your heartbeat is so calming...
I can't take this anymore.
Am I right?
I told you, you're wrong.
I hate it when people mess with you.
Because you said you like me.
I'll always be by your side.